(Bernadette:)Oh, sure,
so it's time when you say it.
(Howard:)Sorry we're late.
I wanted to swing by the lab
(Howard:)and pick up some even
cooler tools for us to use.
(Raj:)-I didn't know you were coming again.
-Wall, last week was a blast.
(Howard:)Plus, I thought you might
like having a guy here.
(Penny(laughing):)It was not funny.
(Amy:)So, what tools did you bring?
(Howard:)Everything we need
to make jewelry molds.
(Howard:)Here's some silver, a crucible
(Howard:)and an acetylene torch
to melt it down.
Ooh! That looks like fun.
(Bernadette:)Maybe you should master glue
before you move on to fire.
(Howard:)Okay, who's up first?
Rajesh, want to make a bracelet
for your mom to go with the necklace?
(Raj:)No, thanks.
(Howard:)I was gonna make
a necklace for my mom,
(Howard:)but unfortunately,
she doesn't have a neck.
(Howard:)She's just chins and fat and feet.
(Leonard:)Okay, we're almost ready to go.
(Leonard:)Once we bond the wires,
we can test the tubes.
This is so exciting, I feel...